Finding Aid for Center for Russian and East European Studies (University of Michigan) records 1957-1997
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Audio Materials
  - Cassette Tapes
    - Sobchak, Anatoly "Press Conference" at the University of Michigan (Box 8)
      (The same conference can be found on video tape)
    - Micro-cassettes (Box 8)
    - Narusova, Liudmila "Public Lecture", February 27, 1995 (Box 8)
    - Sobchak, "Public Lecture", February 28, 1995 (Box 8)
    - Sobchak "Honors I", February 1995 (Box 8)
Related Material
Publications of the Center for Russian and East European Studies are described in a separate finding aid.